

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

#### CONTACTS

+38(099) 401-62-15



denispavlenko94@gmail.com

<u>denis-pavlenko</u>

## **SKILLS SUMMARY**

**HTML** CSS SaSS/SCSS Responsive web pages **JavaScript** Git Gulp Figma/Photoshop/Adobe XD

## **LANGUAGES**

**Ukrainian Native English Intermediate** Russian

#### **PROFILE**

As a Front-End Developer, I have technical knowledge and practical experience in functional programming.

I'm self-motivated and open to new concepts, making me a great team player who adapts quickly to changing environments. I'm passionate about my work and committed to learning and growing as a Front-End Developer.

Joining a team of experts would enhance my skills and provide an opportunity to contribute to exciting projects.

## **PROJECTS**

<u>MoGo</u> click to open project

AXIT Desire **SpiderShiba ElectricCar** 

Football Apparel



GitHub

GitHub

**GitHub** 

## **GitHub GitHub**

technical support for websites

development process

## WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-End Developer at Overall Future

May 2022 - Apr 2023

**Front-End Developer** Freelance

May 2022 - till now

**Account & Project** Manager at IconPartners

July 2020 - Apr 2022

at IT Svit

Lead administrator

at Hillel IT School

Sept 2017 - Dec 2019

Dec 2019 - June 2020

**Account Manager** 

· Selling services and courses

• Budget planning and expense reporting

• Handling incoming applications and calls

• Customer support at every stage of sales

• Setting up programs on computers

Administrator, leather goods store

Oct 2014 - Sept 2017

• Processing of incoming applications, selling

· Filling site content

• Lead generation

• Preparation and execution of documents for shipment

• Developing and maintaining a new and existing projects

• Collaborating with the code developed by others and provide

• Learn and apply new technologies and tools to improve the

• Developing and maintaining HTML/CSS/JS code for web pages

• Preparing technical specifications/statements of work for the team

· Creating responsive and cross-browser web pages

• Maintaining and updating existing websites as needed

• Organizing and participating in negotiations with clients

Conducting weekly analyses of the legal team's reports

• Implementing quality control of the services provided

# **EDUCATION HISTORY**

2014 - 2019, Applied Mechanics, Master's degree

National Technical University "Kharkiv Polytechnic Institute"

2010 - 2014, Applied Mechanics

Kharkiv Mechanical Engineering College

2014 - 2015, Economist, technician with a plan

Kharkiv Mechanical Engineering College

## ADDITIONAL EDUCATION

- Course: "Front-end Basic: HTML&CSS"
- Course: "Front-End Pro: JavaScript"
- Course: "English" Big Bang! English space